export const nature = [
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20moons%2C%20Miranda%2C%20Ariel%2C%20Umbriel%2C%20Titania%20and%20Oberon%20orbit%20which%20planet%3F",
"correct_answer": "Uranus",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jupiter",
"Venus",
"Neptune"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20humerus%2C%20paired%20radius%2C%20and%20ulna%20come%20together%20to%20form%20what%20joint%3F",
"correct_answer": "Elbow",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Knee",
"Sholder",
"Ankle"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20aeronautics%2C%20flaps%20and%20slats%20are%20used%20to%20control%20what%20on%20an%20aircraft%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lift",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Thrust",
"Drag",
"Weight%20"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20first%20living%20creature%20in%20space%3F",
"correct_answer": "Fruit%20Flies%20",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Monkey",
"Dog",
"Mouse"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20mineral%20has%20the%20lowest%20number%20on%20the%20Mohs%20scale%3F",
"correct_answer": "Talc",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Quartz",
"Diamond",
"Gypsum"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Gannymede%20is%20the%20largest%20moon%20of%20which%20planet%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jupiter",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Uranus",
"Neptune",
"Mars"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20degrees%20Fahrenheit%20is%20100%20degrees%20Celsius%3F%20",
"correct_answer": "212",
"incorrect_answers": [
"326",
"100",
"451"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "To%20the%20nearest%20minute%2C%20how%20long%20does%20it%20take%20for%20light%20to%20travel%20from%20the%20Sun%20to%20the%20Earth%3F",
"correct_answer": "8%20Minutes",
"incorrect_answers": [
"6%20Minutes",
"2%20Minutes",
"12%20Minutes"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20chemical%20element%20has%20the%20lowest%20boiling%20point%3F",
"correct_answer": "Helium",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hydrogen",
"Neon",
"Nitrogen"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Au%20on%20the%20Periodic%20Table%20refers%20to%20which%20element%3F",
"correct_answer": "Gold",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Silver",
"Oxygen",
"Nickel"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20psychological%20term%20refers%20to%20the%20stress%20of%20holding%20contrasting%20beliefs%3F",
"correct_answer": "Cognitive%20Dissonance",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Flip-Flop%20Syndrome",
"Split-Brain",
"Blind%20Sight"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20%22Tibia%22%20is%20found%20in%20which%20part%20of%20the%20body%3F",
"correct_answer": "Leg",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Arm",
"Hand",
"Head"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20chemical%20formula%20for%20ammonia%3F",
"correct_answer": "NH3",
"incorrect_answers": [
"CO2",
"NO3",
"CH4"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20polymer%20is%20used%20to%20make%20CDs%2C%20safety%20goggles%20and%20riot%20shields%3F",
"correct_answer": "Polycarbonate",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Rubber",
"Nylon",
"Bakelite"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20medical%20condition%20osteoporosis%20affects%20which%20part%20of%20the%20body%3F",
"correct_answer": "Bones",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Skin",
"Brain",
"Heart"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20a%20part%20of%20the%20structure%20of%20a%20typical%20neuron%3F",
"correct_answer": "Islets%20of%20Langerhans",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Node%20of%20Ranvier",
"Schwann%20cell",
"Myelin%20sheath"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20scientists%20conducted%20the%20Gold%20Foil%20Experiment%20which%20concluded%20that%20atoms%20are%20mostly%20made%20of%20empty%20space%3F",
"correct_answer": "Ernest%20Rutherford",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Joseph%20John%20Thomson",
"Archimedes",
"Niels%20Henrik%20David%20Bohr"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "After%20which%20Danish%20city%20is%20the%2072th%20element%20on%20the%20periodic%20table%20named%3F",
"correct_answer": "Copenhagen",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Odense",
"Herning",
"Skagen"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20a%20type%20of%20stretch%2Fdeep%20tendon%20reflex%3F",
"correct_answer": "Ankle%20jerk%20reflex",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Gag%20reflex",
"Pupillary%20light%20reflex",
"Scratch%20reflex"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20does%20the%20yellow%20diamond%20on%20the%20NFPA%20704%20fire%20diamond%20represent%3F",
"correct_answer": "Reactivity",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Health",
"Flammability",
"Radioactivity"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20human%20right%20lung%20has%20how%20many%20lobes%3F",
"correct_answer": "3",
"incorrect_answers": [
"4",
"2",
"1"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Chemistry%2C%20how%20many%20isomers%20does%20Butanol%20%28C4H9OH%29%20have%3F",
"correct_answer": "4",
"incorrect_answers": [
"3",
"5",
"6"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20stage%20of%20development%20do%20the%20majority%20of%20eukaryotic%20cells%20remain%20in%20for%20most%20of%20their%20life%3F",
"correct_answer": "Interphase",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Prophase",
"Stasis",
"Telophase"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20elements%20on%20the%20Periodic%20Table%20is%20a%20Noble%20Gas%3F",
"correct_answer": "Neon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Potassium",
"Iodine",
"Colbalt"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Deuterium%20is%20an%20isotope%20of%20which%20element%3F",
"correct_answer": "Hydrogen",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nitrogen",
"Helium",
"Neon"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "A%20positron%20is%20an%20antiparticle%20of%20a%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Electron",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Neutron",
"Proton",
"Photon"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20made%20the%20discovery%20of%20X-rays%3F",
"correct_answer": "Wilhelm%20Conrad%20R%C3%B6ntgen",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Thomas%20Alva%20Edison",
"James%20Watt",
"Albert%20Einstein"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "About%20how%20old%20is%20Earth%3F",
"correct_answer": "4.5%20Billion%20Years",
"incorrect_answers": [
"3.5%20Billion%20Years",
"2.5%20Billion%20Years",
"5.5%20Billion%20Years"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20unit%20of%20electrical%20capacitance%3F",
"correct_answer": "Farad",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Gauss",
"Henry",
"Watt"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Psychology%2C%20which%20need%20appears%20highest%20in%20the%20%22Maslow%27s%20hierarchy%20of%20needs%22%20pyramid%3F",
"correct_answer": "Esteem",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Love",
"Safety",
"Physiological"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20are%20human%20nails%20made%20of%3F",
"correct_answer": "Keratin",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bone",
"Chitin",
"Calcium"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "On%20which%20mission%20did%20the%20Space%20Shuttle%20Columbia%20break%20up%20upon%20re-entry%3F",
"correct_answer": "STS-107",
"incorrect_answers": [
"STS-51-L",
"STS-61-C",
"STS-109"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20part%20of%20the%20brain%20takes%20its%20name%20from%20the%20Greek%20for%20seahorse%3F",
"correct_answer": "Hippocampus",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Cerebellum",
"Thalamus",
"Amygdala"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20planet%20did%20the%20%22Viking%201%22%20spacecraft%20send%20surface%20images%20of%2C%20starting%20in%201976%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mars",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Saturn",
"Jupiter",
"Venus"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Approximately%20how%20long%20is%20a%20year%20on%20Uranus%3F",
"correct_answer": "84%20Earth%20years",
"incorrect_answers": [
"47%20Earth%20years",
"62%20Earth%20years",
"109%20Earth%20years"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Down%20Syndrome%20is%20usually%20caused%20by%20an%20extra%20copy%20of%20which%20chromosome%3F",
"correct_answer": "21",
"incorrect_answers": [
"23",
"15",
"24"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20half-life%20of%20Uranium-235%3F",
"correct_answer": "703%2C800%2C000%20years",
"incorrect_answers": [
"4%2C300%2C400%2C000%20years",
"1%2C260%2C900%2C000%20years",
"Uranium-235%20is%20a%20stable%20isotope"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "On%20the%20periodic%20table%20of%20elements%2C%20what%20is%20the%20symbol%20for%20Tin%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sn",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ti",
"Ni",
"Na"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20human%20biology%2C%20a%20circadium%20rhythm%20relates%20to%20a%20period%20of%20roughly%20how%20many%20hours%3F",
"correct_answer": "24",
"incorrect_answers": [
"8",
"16",
"32"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20medial%20meniscus%20forms%20which%20part%20of%20what%20joint%20in%20the%20human%20body%3F",
"correct_answer": "Knee",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Elbow",
"Ankle",
"Shoulder"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "An%20organism%20described%20as%20%22heliotropic%22%20has%20a%20tendancy%20to%20move%20towards%20which%20of%20these%20things%3F",
"correct_answer": "Light",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Water",
"Trees",
"Pollen"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20Linnean%20name%20of%20the%20domestic%20apple%20tree%3F",
"correct_answer": "Malus%20pumila",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Malus%20americana",
"Pomus%20domestica",
"Appelus%20delectica"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20spacecraft%20never%20touched%20the%20moon%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mariner%204",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Apollo%2011",
"Luna%202",
"SMART-1"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Deionized%20water%20is%20water%20with%20which%20of%20the%20following%20removed%3F",
"correct_answer": "Iron",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Oxygen",
"Hydrogen",
"Uncharged%20atoms"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20choices%20is%20not%20one%20of%20the%20phases%20of%20mitosis%3F",
"correct_answer": "Diplophase",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Metaphase",
"Anaphase",
"Telophase"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20cognitive%20bias%20wherein%20a%20person%20with%20low%20ability%20in%20a%20particular%20skill%20mistake%20themselves%20as%20being%20superior%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dunning-Kruger%20effect",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Meyers-Briggs%20effect",
"M%C3%BCller-Lyer%20effect",
"Freud-Hall%20effect"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20Hypernatremia%3F",
"correct_answer": "Increase%20in%20blood%20sodium",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Decrease%20in%20blood%20potassium",
"Increase%20in%20blood%20glucose",
"Decrease%20in%20blood%20iron"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20an%20alternative%20name%20for%20multiple%20personality%20disorder%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dissociative%20identity%20disorder",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Body%20integrity%20identity%20disorder",
"Identity%20crisis",
"Schizophrenia"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "When%20was%20the%20first%20mammal%20successfully%20cloned%3F",
"correct_answer": "1996",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2009",
"1999",
"1985"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20old%20is%20the%20universe%3F",
"correct_answer": "13.8%20Billion%20Years",
"incorrect_answers": [
"4.5%20Billion%20Years",
"7.9%20Billion%20Years",
"16.2%20Billion%20Years"
]
}
]